He's a washed-up loser. But sometimes losers can be heroes...
The Electric Horseman is a drama, romance, comedy
film directed by Sydney Pollack.
A former champion rodeo rider is reduced to using his saddle skills to
promote a breakfast cereal in a gaudy Las Vegas show.
When he's asked to perform with a $12 million horse, he
discovers it is being doped to remain docile.
He flees into the desert astride the beast in an act of defiance.
A story-hungry female reporter gives chase.
Sonny, played by Robert Redford.
Hallie, played by Jane Fonda.
Charlotta, played by Valerie Perrine.
Wendell, played by Willie Nelson.
Hunt Sears, played by John Saxon.
Fitzgerald, played by Nicolas Coster.
The Electric Horseman is a 1979 American Western comedy-drama film starring
Robert Redford and Jane Fonda and directed by Sydney Pollack.
The film is about a former rodeo champion who is hired by a cereal company to become its spokesperson, and then runs away on a $12
million electric-lit horse and costume he is given to promote it in Las Vegas after he finds that the horse has been abused.
The film explores themes of rodeo, horse, doping, love, cowboy.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.